Dan Mark B. Diza

3444 Keele St., Toronto, ON M3J1L8 (647) 8850-0719 dmdiza@my.yorku.ca

24th February 2020

Hiring Manager

S&C Electric Canada Inc. 90 Belfield Rd, Toronto, ON M5B 1K5

Dear Hiring Manager, \

Through my college education and the current electrical courses, I have gained extensive knowledge in various electronic components (diodes, transistors, resistors, LED, etc). The Assistant QA Inspector position at S&C Electric Canada would significantly help me hone and further improve my knowledge in Electronics. After graduating from Seneca, I gained experience in electronics manufacturing. I assembled and tested various circuits along with calibration of various conformal coating machines.

For the past 2 years that I was working as a Part-Time Meat Clerk. I have demonstrated excellent communication and interpersonal skills to build rapport with customers and answer customers' questions clearly and concisely. Collaboration is a crucial part of my job at Loblaws, I have no difficulty in working alone or in a team. My colleagues have commended my ability to work and get along with everyone and I have also established good rapport amongst my colleagues.

Throughout my academic career, extracurricular roles, and the part-time job I have demonstrated the ability to work under pressure to finish a task that requires analytical and problem-solving skills.

I look forward to meeting with you to discuss the role by calling me at (647)885-0719. I am eligible for up to 16 months of full-time coop position starting this May 2020. Besides, I am willing to relocate and work various shifts to fulfill the job requirements.

Sincerely,

Dan Mark Diza

Dan Mark B. Diza

🗣 3444 Keele St., Toronto, ON M3J 1L8 🔀 dmdiza@my.yorku.ca 📞 6478850719 🛮 in linkedin.com/in/dmdiza

Looking to secure an Engineering Co-op position to apply and further my skills and knowledge in electrical theory, programming, and various electronic devices such as diodes, transistors, and op-amps. In addition to my knowledge, I'm also adept in using various testing equipment such as oscilloscopes, function generator, digital multi-meters, and DC power supply.

SKILLS

Technical Skills

Java, C/C++, Matlab, BASH, Circuit Analysis, Electronics Assembly, Device Troubleshooting, MS Office, Soldering Skills, LTSpice, Visual Basic, Verilog

Lab Equipments

Oscilloscope, Function Generator, Digital Multimeters

Interpersonal Skills

Leadership, Communications, Customer Service, Team Work, Problem Solving, Time Managment

Media Skills

Photography, Lightroom, Graphics Design, Event Photography

EDUCATION

Lassonde School of Engineering, York University, Bachelors of Engineering, Electrical Engineering

September 2018 - present

Toronto, ON

Seneca College of Applied Arts and Technology, Advance Diploma, Electronics Engineering Technology Graduated with a GPA of 3.2 out of 4

September 2013 - May 2016

March 2017 - November 2017

Toronto, ON

WORK EXPERIENCE

Loblaws, Part Time Meat Clerk

• Provide excellent customer service to achieve high customer satisfaction rate

2017 - present Toronto, ON

Toronto, ON

- Maintain cleanliness of department and the high quality of meat products
- Reduce daily inventory loss from 40% to 10% by implementing steeper mark downs.
- Lead a team of 3 clerks to maintain the stock level during a busy day
- Efficiently train new colleagues to perform various task within department.

Custom Rapid Solutions, Manufacturing Technician

- Apply conformal coat to weather sensitive circuits boards
- Perform inspection and testing of circuit boards that resulted in low item returns
- Assemble and package circuit boards for shipment
- Soldered electric components to circuit boards with low rework rate

EXTRACURRICULAR ROLES

Lassonde Media Group, Creative Director

May 2019 - present • Design marketing materials for club events that resulted in higher event turnouts York University, Toronto, ON

- Create online content for the club's Youtube Channel
- Edit photos using Adobe Lightroom to produce premium quality event photos
- Coordinate a team of 5 to assure all club tasks are being completed

IEEE YorkU Student Branch, Vice President - Media

May 2019 - present • Handle overall club communications to successfully market the club events York University, Toronto, ON

- Plan technical and social events for electrical and computer engineering students
- Coordinate 2 or more volunteers to successfully run social and technical events.
- Design marketing posters that resulted in higher event turnouts

Lassonde School of Engineering, Orientation Week Leader & Media Personnel

- Provided photo and video coverage for various faculty social events
- Ensured that all incoming students are safe and properly accommodated
- Volunteers to manage a team of leaders to successfully finish an assigned task
- Supervise 20 leaders to ensure that every first year student is not left alone

PROJECTS

Wifi Controlled Surveillance Car

The project was implemented using Arduino Mega, Raspberry Pi, Motors, and sensors. The car is able to detect a cliff and obstacles, the car will stop upon detection. In addition, there is camera the provides lives stream via a laptop.

Green Home Monitoring System

Implemented a program for power consumption and monitoring system using C. The system measure power consumption and ensures that power is not wasted. System was deployed using two (2) HCS08 microcontrollers and serial communication was used to allow communication between the 2 microcontrollers.

January 2016 - May 2016

March 2015 - April 2015

August 2019 - August 2019

York University, Toronto, ON

List of Courses and Grades

Dan Mark Baggayan Diza 903-3444 Keele St, Toronto, ON M3J 1L8

Update Address

This is not an official transcript.

Session	Course	Title	Grade
FW19	LE EECS 2021 4.00 E	Computer Organization	C+
FW19	LE EECS 2030 3.00 E	Advanced Object Oriented Programming	
FW19	LE EECS 2032 4.00 Z	Introduction to Embedded Systems	in progress
FW19	LE EECS 2200 3.00 E	Electrical Circuits	B+
FW19	LE EECS 2210 3.00 Z	Electronic Circuits and Devices	in progress
FW19	LE EECS 2602 4.00 Z	Signals and Systems in Continuous Time	in progress
FW19	LE ENG 2003 3.00 O	Effective Engineering Communication	in progress
FW19	SC PHYS 2020 3.00 E	Electricity and Magnetism	D
FW19	SC PHYS 2211 1.00 M	Experimental Electromagnetism	in progress
SU19	LE ENG 2001 3.00 A	Eng Projs:Management, Economics & Safety	C+
SU19	SC MATH 2015 3.00 M	Applied Multivariate & Vector Calculus	B+
SU19	SC MATH 2930 3.00 A	Engineering Statistics	C+
FW18	LE EECS 1011 3.00 E	Computational Thinking	B+
FW18	LE EECS 1021 3.00 Z	Object Oriented Programming	В
FW18	LE EECS 1028 3.00 M	Discrete Mathematics for Engineers	C+
FW18	LE ENG 1101 4.00 A	Renaissance Engineer 1:	A
FW18	LE ENG 1102 4.00 M	Ren. Eng. 2: Eng. Design Principles	A
FW18	SC MATH 1013 3.00 A	Applied Calculus I	В
FW18	SC MATH 1014 3.00 Q	Applied Calculus II	D
FW18	SC MATH 1025 3.00 A	Applied Linear Algebra	С
FW18	SC PHYS 1800 3.00 A	Engineering Mechanics	С
FW18	SC PHYS 1801 3.00 M	Electricity, Magnetism & Optics for Eng.	B+

This information is valid as at Jan 09, 2020 09:42 PM

Other Grade Reports

View grades, academic decisions and GPA by session:

Summer Grade Report: View your Summer grade report here

Fall/Winter Grade Report: View your Fall/Winter grade report here

Grades for Other Sessions: View a full list of your courses and grades here

Attention Undergraduate students!

Many questions you may have about grade reports will be answered by viewing our multimedia presentation called <u>Understanding Your Undergraduate Grade Report</u>

Students in the Faculty of Liberal Arts and Professional Studies are strongly encouraged to view the helpful multimedia presentation "Understanding Your Academic Standing" available here.

Here are quick answers to some of the more commonly asked questions about grades:

What do I do if I have a missing or blank grade?

Grades will be blank until they are officially reported at the conclusion of the course and, where applicable, associated exam. Grades must be reported no later than 5 business days after the exam period. If, after this time, you still have a blank fall term grade, contact your professor or the department offering the course and ask when the grade will be reported.

Can my grades change?

Grades appear incrementally as they are reported by your course instructors and/or department. Grades may change after appearing in your online grade report as a result of further review by your program, Faculty or instructor.

What does NGR mean?

NGR means No Grade Reported. Please contact your professor or the department offering the course to inquire when the grade will be reported.

What does F NGR mean?

F NGR means that a grade of F will be on your record until another grade is reported by your professor.

What do I do if a grade was reported incorrectly?

First, contact your professor to confirm the grade reported. Then, if you wish to appeal a grade, you will find information on grade reappraisals here: http://www.registrar.yorku.ca/grades/reappraisal

What do I do if my grade report says I am ineligible to continue or I want to talk with someone about my degree program options?

Contact your Faculty advising office here: http://acadresources.yorku.ca/advising/

Where do I find out more Faculty-specific information about my grade report?

Each Faculty has a grades legend here: http://www.registrar.yorku.ca/grades/legends

Other important information

How can I order an official transcript of my grades?

Go here: http://www.registrar.yorku.ca/transcripts for information on transcripts.